A Guide to the Correspondence and Subject files of the Virginia Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 1972-2006
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Virginia Secretary of Health and Human Resources Correspondence and Subject files, 1972-2006
The Library of Virginia
31515, 32692, 33417, 33719, 34301, 34553, 35147, 35869, 37779
cu. ft. ( boxes)
Virginia. Secretary of Health and Human Resources.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred from the Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 6 October 1982 [Accession 31515].
Transferred from the Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 3 April 1986 [Accession 32692].
Transferred from the Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 23 February 1989 [Accession 33417].
Transferred from the Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 1 February 1990 [Accession 33719].
Transferred from the Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 30 October 1992 [Accession 34301].
Transferred from the Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 1 December 1993 [Accession 34553].
Transferred from the Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 11 November 1996 [Accession 35147].
Transferred from the Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 19 June 1998 [Accession 35869].
Transferred from the Secretary of Health and Human Resources, Unknown [Accession 37779].
Biographical Information
The secretariat responsible for human services, health and welfare has gone through several reorganizations. In 1972, the General Assembly passed an act establishing the Secretary of Human Affairs. This office was responsible for management and direction of health and human services provided by the state for the citizens of the commonwealth. In 1976, the secretariat's name changed to the Secretary of Human Resources. With reorganization of state government, the secretariat's name changed again to the Secretary of Health and Human Resources in 1988. The secretary has authority over the following agencies or councils: Dept. for the Rights of Virginians with Disabilities; Dept. for the Aging; State Dept. of Health; Dept. of Health Professionals; Dept. of Medical Assistance Services; Virginia Health Services Cost Review Council; Dept. of Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services; Dept. of Rehabilitation Services; Dept. of Social Services; Governors Employment and Training Dept.; Dept. for the Deaf and Hard of Hearing; Virginia Council on Child Care & Early Childhood Programs. The Secretary also serves on several advisory councils, committees, boards, and interstate compacts.
Scope and Content
Records, 1970-1998, consisting of the incoming and outgoing correspondence of the Secretary of Health and Human Resources with the Governor's Office, state agencies, localities, other secretariats, and the private sector. The correspondence is related to various health and social issues which affect the citizens of the Commonwealth.
Topics include aging, health, welfare, Social Security Act Title XX, refugee resettlement, disabled children, WIC and Food Stamp programs, mental health and mental retardation, and nutrition.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I: Correspondence and subject files, 1970-1981 [Accession 31515]
Series II: Correspondence and subject files, 1982-1986 [Accession 32692]
Series III: Correspondence and subject files, 1983 [Accession 33417]
Series IV: Correspondence and subject files, 1984-1989 [Accession 33719]
Series V: Correspondence and subject files, 1987-1989 [Accession 34301]
Series VI: Correspondence and subject files, 1990-1992 [Accession 34553]
Series VII: Correspondence and subject files, 1993-1994 [Accession 35147]
Series VIII: Correspondence and subject files, 1994-1997 [Accession 35869]
Series IX: Correspondence and subject files, 1970-1991 [Accession 37779]
Contents List
- Series I: Correspondence and subject files, [Accession 31515], 1970-1981, Extent: cu. ft. (boxes). (Box 1-)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Virginia Council for the Deaf, 1978-1981 (Box 1)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Health Regulatory Boards, Virginia Board of Dentistry, 1978-1981 (Box 1)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Health Regulatory Boards, State Board of Medicine, 1978-1981 (Box 1)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Health Regulatory Boards, State Board of Nursing, 1978-1981 (Box 1)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Guide to Federal Resources for the Developmentally Disabled, 1978-1981 (Box 1)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Division for Children, 1978-1981 (Box 2)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Commission on the Status of Women, 1978-1981 (Box 2)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Welfare, Division of Administration, 1978-1981 (Box 2)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Welfare, Board, 1978-1981 (Box 2)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Welfare, Legislation, 1978-1981 (Box 2)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Welfare, Welfare reform, 1978-1981 (Box 3)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Welfare, Food Stamp program, 1978-1981 (Box 3)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Welfare, Personnel, 1978-1981 (Box 3)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Welfare, Division of Social Services, 1978-1981 (Box 3)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Social Security Act (Title XX), 1978-1981 (Box 3)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Social Security Act (Titles IV-A and VI), 1978-1981 (Box 4)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Feasibility Study, "A Statewide System of Health Information and Referral Services for Virginia," 1978-1981 (Box 4)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Social Services Draft Plan (Title XX), 1978-1981 (Box 4)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Comprehensive Annual Plan for Social Services Under Title XX of the National Social Security Act, 1978-1981 (Box 4)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Commonwealth of Virginia, Draft Comprehensive Annual Plan for Social Services Under Title XX of the National Security Act, 1978-1981 (Box 4)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Demonstration Project in Long Term Care Review by Colonial Virginia Foundation for Medical Care, 1978-1981 (Box 4)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Southwest Virginia Professional Standards Review, 1978-1981 (Box 4)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Central Virginia Health Systems Agency Inc., HSA Application, 1978-1981 (Box 4)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Shenandoah Professional Standards Review Foundation, Long term care plan, 1978-1981 (Box 4)
  - Health, Dept. of, Health Planning and Resource Development Division, 1978-1981 (Box 5)
  - Health, Dept. of, General, 1978-1981 (Box 5)
  - Health, Dept. of, Emergency Medical Services, 1978-1981 (Box 5)
  - Health, Dept. of, Bureau of Family Planning, 1978-1981 (Box 5)
  - Health, Dept. of, Local Health Services, 1978-1981 (Box 5)
  - Health, Dept. of, Medicaid, Medical Assistance Program, 1978-1981 (Box 6)
  - Health, Dept. of, Bureau of Shellfish Sanitation, 1978-1981 (Box 6)
  - Health, Dept. of, Personnel, 1978-1981 (Box 6)
  - Health, Dept. of, Kings Dominion, 1978-1981 (Box 6)
  - Health, Dept. of, Legislation, 1978-1981 (Box 6)
  - Health, Dept. of, Kepone Task Force, 1978-1981 (Box 6)
  - Health, Dept. of, Statistical Annual Report, 1975 (Box 7)
  - Health, Dept. of, Virginia Tumor Registry, 1978-1981 (Box 7)
  - Health, Dept. of, National Health Resources Advisory Committee Meeting Report, 1974 (Box 7)
  - Health, Dept. of, Rural Affairs Study Commission, Notes on Health Care in Rural Virginia, 1970 (Box 7)
  - Health, Dept. of, Medical Care Review (Vol. 33, No. 9), 1976 October (Box 7)
  - Health, Dept. of, National Health Insurance Proposals, 1974 (Box 7)
  - Health, Dept. of, Orientation Programs for newly Employed Public Health Personnel, 1978-1981 (Box 7)
  - Health, Dept. of, Application for full designation of a health systems agency for Eastern Virginia (Eastern Virginia Health Systems Agency Inc.), 1978-1981 (Box 7)
  - Health, Dept. of, Proposal for a Demonstration Project Long Term Care Review, Colonial Virginia Foundation for Medical Care, 1978-1981 (Box 7)
  - Health, Dept. of, Commonwealth of Virginia, Application for full designation as the State HEalth Planning and Development Agency, 1978-1981 (Box 7)
  - Health, Dept. of, Health Service Areas, 1978-1981 (Box 7)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Rehabilitative Services, International Year of Disabled Persons, 1978-1981 (Box 8)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Rehabilitative Services, Sheltered workshops, 1978-1981 (Box 8)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Vocational Rehabilitation, Woodrow Wilson Center of Rehabilitation, 1978-1981 (Box 8)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Rehabilitative Services, General, 1978-1981 (Box 8)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Rehabilitative Services, General, 1978-1981 (Box 9)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Board, 1978-1981 (Box 10)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, S.B. 281, 1978-1981 (Box 10)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Personnel (Review for privacy), 1978-1981 (Box 10)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Contract Management of State Mental Hospitals, 1978-1981 (Box 10)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Division of Substance Abuse, 1978-1981 (Box 10)
  - Human Resources, Office of, General Assembly, Commission on Mental Health and Mental Retardation, H.B. 1935, 1978-1981 (Box 10)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, General, 1978-1981 (Box 11)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Vocational Rehabilitation, Summary statement, 1978-1981 (Box 11)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Vocational Rehabilitation, Report on Audit, 1978-1981 (Box 11)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Va. Dept. of Vocational Rehabilitation, Agreements and MOU, 1978-1981 (Box 11)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Rehabilitative Services, General, 1978-1981 (Box 12)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Vocational Rehabilitation, General, 1978-1981 (Box 12)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Vocational Rehabilitation, JLARC Report, 1978-1981 (Box 12)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Vocational Rehabilitation, General, 1978-1981 (Box 13)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Vocational Rehabilitation, Confidential file (Review for privacy), 1978-1981 (Box 13)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Vocational Rehabilitation, Division of Information Services, 1978-1981 (Box 13)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Vocational Rehabilitation, Personnel (Review for privacy), 1978-1981 (Box 13)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Aging, General, 1978-1981 (Box 13)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Developmental Disabilities Planning and Advisory Council, 1978-1981 (Box 14)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Developmental Disabilities Protection and Advisory Council, 1978-1981 (Box 14)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Committee for the Visually Handicapped, General, 1978-1981 (Box 14)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. on Aging, General, 1978-1981 (Box 15)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. on Aging, State Plan on Aging, 1978 (Box 15)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. on Aging, Aging budget, 1976 (Box 15)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. on Children and Youth, General, 1978-1981 (Box 16)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. on Children and Youth, Newsletters, 1976-1978 (Box 16)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Virginia's Children: A Statistical Study, 1978 (Box 16)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Report of the 1st National Workshop for State Committees for Children and Youth, 1973 (Box 16)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Virginia Commission on Children and Youth, Bylaws, 1972 (Box 16)
  - Human Resources, Office of, You have the right, if you know it: A Rights and Responsibilities Handbook, 1976 (Box 16)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Report of the Governor's Youth Council, 1973 (Box 16)
  - Human Resources, Office of, What kids can do, National Commission on Resources for Youth, Inc., 1973 (Box 16)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Virginia's Children and Youth, A report to the Governor and General Assembly, 1974 (Box 16)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Virginia's Children and Youth, White House Conference, 1970 (Box 16)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Virginia Council for the Deaf, General, 1978-1981 (Box 16)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Deaf and Blind, Education, 1978-1981 (Box 17)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Virginia Employment Commission, CETA Program (Comprehensive Employment and Training Act), 1978-1981 (Box 17)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Virginia Employment Commission, General, 1978-1981 (Box 17)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Virginia Employment Commission, Balance of State Planning Council, 1978-1981 (Box 18)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Governor's Employment and Training Council, 1978-1981 (Box 18)
  - Governor, Office of, Governor's Employment and Training Council, 1978-1981 (Box 19)
  - Study of the Manpower Services Program in Virginia, Draft report, 1979 (Box 19)
  - Study of the Manpower Services Program in Virginia, Final report, 1978-1981 (Box 19)
  - Governor, Office of, Governor's Manpower Planning Council, 1978-1981 (Box 20)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Virginia Employment Commission, Balance of State Planning Council, 1978-1981 (Box 20)
  - ES-UI Realignment Study, 1978-1981 (Box 20)
  - ES-UI Realignment Study, Conducted by Virginia Employment Commission, 1978-1981 (Box 20)
  - Comparative Study of State Employment Security Agencies with Separate ES-UI Organizations, 1978-1981 (Box 20)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Virginia Employment Commission, CETA Program, 1978-1981 (Box 20)
  - Human Resources, Secretary of (Dr. Jean Harris), Private Industry Council meeting minutes and agendas, 1978-1981 (Box 20)
  - Virginia Employment Commission, Fiscal Year 1980 Program and Budget Plan, 1978-1981 (Box 20)
  - Study of Richmond Area Employers and Employment Activities, 1978 (Box 20)
  - Examination and Impact Assessment of PIC Organization and Operation in Virginia, Appendix, 1978-1981 (Box 20)
  - Examination and Impact Assessment of PIC Organization and Operation in Virginia, Executive Summary, 1978-1981 (Box 20)
  - Examination and Impact Assessment of PIC Organization and Operation in Virginia, Final report, 1978-1981 (Box 20)
  - Governor, Office of, Governor's Employment and Training Council, 1978-1981 (Box 21)
  - Governor, Office of, Governor's Manpower Services Council, 1978-1981 (Box 21)
  - Annual Employment and Training Report to the Governor of Virginia, 1978 (Box 21)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Virginia Employment Commission, General, 1978-1981 (Box 21)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Virginia Employment Commission, Information Services, Newsletters, 1976-1979 (Box 22)
  - U.S. Employment and Training Report of the President, 1978 (Box 22)
  - Virginia Employment Commission, Project status and Financial report, Public Employment Program, 1978-1981 (Box 22)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Virginia Employment Commission, CETA Program, 1978-1981 (Box 22)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Virginia Employment Commission, General, 1978-1981 (Box 22)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Virginia Employment Commission, General, 1978-1981 (Box 23)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Virginia Employment Commission, CETA Program, 1978-1981 (Box 23)
  - Governor, Office of, Governor's Manpower Planning Council, 1978-1981 (Box 23)
  - General Assembly, Migrant and Seasonal Farmworkers Commission (H.B. 258), 1978 (Box 24)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Virginia Employment Commission, Disaster Unemployment Assistance, 1978-1981 (Box 24)
  - Study of the Manpower Services Program in Virginia, Executive Summary, 1979 (Box 24)
  - "Virginia Labor Market Information Review- Richmond," 1979 (Box 24)
  - "Virginia Labor Market Information Review- Northern Neck-Hampton," 1979 (Box 24)
  - "Virginia Labor Market Information Review- Lynchburg-Roanoke," 1979 (Box 24)
  - "Virginia Labor Market Information Review- Norfolk-Portsmouth," 1979 (Box 24)
  - "Virginia Labor Market Information Review- Petersburg," 1979 (Box 24)
  - Employment Assistance Services within the Human Resources Agencies, Position paper, 1978-1981 (Box 24)
  - Virginia Balance-of-State Modification No. 903 to Prime Sponsor Agreements, 1978-1981 (Box 24)
  - Virginia Balance-of-State Annual and Fiscal plan, 1979 (Box 24)
  - Virginia Employment Commission, Annual Planning Information Report, 1979-1980 (Box 24)
  - Virginia Employment Commission, Annual Planning Information Report, Petersburg SMSA, CETA Prime Sponsor, 1979-1980 (Box 24)
  - Virginia Employment Commission, Annual Planning Information Report, STAMA Consortium, Planning District 20, 1979-1980 (Box 24)
  - Governor, Office of, Governor's Manpower Planning Council, 1978-1981 (Box 24)
  - Virginia Employment Commission, Annual reports, 1974-1975 (Box 25)
  - Virginia Employment Commission, Unemployment Insurance in Virginia, Employers Handbook, 1976 (Box 25)
  - U.S. Dept. of Labor Employment and Training Administration, Catalog, Regional Training Center, Region III, 1978-1981 (Box 25)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Virginia Employment Commission, General, 1978-1981 (Box 25)
  - Governor, Office of, Governor's Manpower Planning Council, 1978-1981 (Box 25)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Virginia Employment Commission, CETA Program, 1978-1981 (Box 25)
  - Annual Report of the Virginia Employment Commission to the Governor, 1975-1977 (Box 26)
  - Virginia Employment Commission, Marymount College of Virginia, Proposal, 1978 (Box 26)
  - U.S. Dept. of Labor, Employment and Training Administration, Employment and Training Programs for Offenders, 1978-1981 (Box 26)
  - Draft Language and Commentary to Implement the Unemployment Compensation Amendments, 1976 (Box 26)
  - U.S. Dept. of Labor, CETA Audit Guide, 1976-1977 (Box 26)
  - Virginia Employment Commission, Implementation Schedule, CETA Reorganization, 1976-1978 (Box 26)
  - Virginia Balance of State, CETA Manpower Planning System, 1978-1981 (Box 26)
  - Proposed organization of the Virginia Employment Commission, 1976 (Box 26)
  - Review of the Virginia Employment Commission Resource Sharing, 1976 (Box 26)
  - Proposed Organization of the Virginia Balance-of-State, Established as a Separate CETA Prime Sponsorship Individual Agency, 1976 (Box 26)
  - Manpower Services Council, CETA, Annual report, 1975 (Box 26)
  - Speeches, Sec. of Human Resources, Dr. Jean L. Harris, 1978-1981 (Box 26)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Issue Status reports, 1978-1981 (Box 26)
  - Human Resources, Secretary of, News clippings, 1978-1981 (Box 27)
  - Human Resources, Secretary of, Biological sketches, 1978-1981 (Box 27)
  - Human Resources, Secretary of, Photographs 1978-1981 (Box 27)
  - Human Resources, Office of, General, 1978-1981 (Box 27)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Budget, 1978-1981 (Box 27)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Personnel (Review for privacy), 1978-1981 (Box 27)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Division of Administration, 1978-1981 (Box 28)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Board, 1978-1981 (Box 28)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Prescription Team, 1978-1981 (Box 28)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Placement of Children, 1978-1981 (Box 28)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Northern Va. Training Center Deinstitutionalization, 1978-1981 (Box 28)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Personnel (Review for privacy), 1978-1981 (Box 28)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Division of Mental Health, 1978-1981 (Box 29)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Division of Mental Retardation, 1978-1981 (Box 29)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, General, 1978-1981 (Box 29)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Service Boards, 1978-1981 (Box 29)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Chapter 10 Service Boards, 1978-1981 (Box 29)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Division of Mental Health, 1978-1981 (Box 30)
  - Fairfax-Falls Church Community Services Board, Alcohol Problems and Programs in the Fairfax Area, A Needs Assessment, 1977-1978 (Box 30)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Fairfax-Falls Church Community Services Board, Comprehensive Five Year Alcoholism Services Plan, 1979 (Box 30)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Division of Administration, 1978-1981 (Box 30)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Data Services Division, 1978-1981 (Box 30)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Division of Program Development and Evaluation, 1978-1981 (Box 30)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Division of Substance Abuse, 1978-1981 (Box 30)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Western State Hospital, 1978-1981 (Box 31)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Division of Administration, 1978-1981 (Box 31)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Personnel (Review for privacy), 1978-1981 (Box 31)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, General, 1978-1981 (Box 31)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Presentation on Community Services Funding to Commission in MH and MR, 1978-1981 (Box 31)
  - Commission on Mental Health and Mental Retardation with National Experts, 1979 (Box 31)
  - Subcommittee on State Administration of the Commission on Mental Health and Mental Retardation, 1978-1981 (Box 31)
  - Subcommittee on Community-Based Services of the Commission on Mental Health and Mental Retardation, 1978-1981 (Box 31)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Division of Administration, 1978-1981 (Box 32)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Board, 1978-1981 (Box 32)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Lynchburg Training School, 1978-1981 (Box 32)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, General, 1978-1981 (Box 32)
  - State Mental Health and Mental Retardation Board, Final report on task force on mental health needs of the elderly, 1978 (Box 32)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Publications on Mental Health, 1978-1981 (Box 32)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Central State Hospital, 1978-1981 (Box 32)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Eastern State Hospital, 1978-1981 (Box 33)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Information Director, 1978-1981 (Box 33)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Legislation (after 1978), 1978-1981 (Box 33)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Psychiatric Institutes, 1969-1974 (Box 33)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, General, 1978-1981 (Box 33)